A Guide to the Office of the President, Special Records, Files of Norma Lane, 1974-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the President, Special Records, Files of Norma Lane 1974-1979
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/3.841
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1984 June 21.
Contents List
- Athletics - Basketball - Re: UVa vs. VPI, January 17, 1979 1978-1919 (Box 1)
- Athletics - Basketball/President's Box - Invitation and Guest Lists 1974-1979, 5 folders (Box 1)
- Athletics - Basketball/President's Box - Parking Information and Miscellaneous Correspondence 1974-1979, 5 folders (Box 1)
- Athletics - Football/President's Box - Commonwealth Day 1974, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Athletics - Football/President's Box - Commonwealth Day 1975-1978, 5 folders (Box 2)
- Athletics - Football/President's Box - Invitation and Guest Lists 1974, 1 of 5 folders (Box 2)
- Athletics - Football/President's Box - Invitation and Guest Lists 1975-1978, folders 2-5 of 5 (Box 3)
- Athletics - Football/President's Box - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1974-1979, 5 folders (Box 3)
- Athletics - Football/President's Box - Scott Family 1974 (Box 3)
- Faculty, New - Orientation and Reception 1974-1979 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - The Artemus Awards 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Information 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Guest Lists 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - The Thomas Jefferson Award 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Program 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Tree Planting 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Information 1976 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Guest Lists 1977 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Program 1977 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Thomas Jefferson Award 1977 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Information 1978 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Guest Lists, Convocation Information 1978 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Program 1978 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - Shannon Garden Dedication 1978 (Box 4)
- Fall Convocation - The Thomas Jefferson Award 1978 (Box 4)
- Finals 1975 - Law School 1975 (Box 5)
- Finals 1975 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1975, 2 folders (Box 5)
- Finals 1975 - Norma Lane's Notes 1975 (Box 5)
- Finals 1975 - President's Remarks 1975 (Box 5)
- Finals 1976 - Law School 1976 (Box 5)
- Finals 1976 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1976, 2 folders (Box 5)
- Finals 1976 - Norma Lane's Notes 1976 (Box 5)
- Finals 1976 - President's Remarks 1976 (Box 5)
- Finals 1977 - Conferring of Degrees Statement 1977 (Box 5)
- Finals 1977 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1977, 2 folders (Box 6)
- Finals 1977 - Norma Lane's Notes 1977 (Box 6)
- Finals 1977 - Program 1977 (Box 6)
- Finals 1978 - Conferring of Degree Outline 1978 (Box 6)
- Finals 1978 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1978, 2 folders (Box 6)
- Finals 1978 - Norma Lane's Notes 1978 (Box 6)
- Finals 1978 - Program 1978 (Box 6)
- Finals - Baccalaureate and Class Day 1979 (Box 6)
- Finals - Conferring of Degrees Outline 1979 (Box 6)
- Finals - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1979, 2 folders (Box 6)
- Finals 1979 - Norma Lane's Notes 1979 (Box 7)
- Finals - Program 1979 (Box 7)
- Founder's Day 1975 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1975, 2 folders (Box 7)
- Founder's Day 1975 - Norma Lane's Notes 1975 (Box 7)
- Founder's Day 1975 - President's Remarks 1975 (Box 7)
- Founder's Day 1975 - Thomas Jefferson Award 1975 (Box 7)
- Founder's Day 1976 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1976, 3 folders (Box 7)
- Founder's Day 1976 - Norma Lane's Notes 1976 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1976 - President's Remarks 1976 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1976 - Rotunda Dedication and Two Dollar Bill Presentation, April 13, 1976 1976 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1976 - Thomas Jefferson Award 1976 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1976 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Medal in Architecture 1976 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1977 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1977 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1977 - Norma Lane's Notes 1977 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1977 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Medal in Architecture 1977 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1977 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Award in Law 1977 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1978 - Jefferson Statue Dedication, North Grounds 1978 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1978 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1978 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1978 - Norma Lane's Notes 1978 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1978 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Award in Architecture 1978 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1978 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Award in Law 1978 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1978 - Tree Planting 1978 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1979 - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Information 1979 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1979 - Norma Lane's Notes 1979 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1979 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Medal in Architecture 1979 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1979 - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Award in Law 1979 (Box 8)